zrii.com 2012-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Zrii

### Privacy Policy

We are proud to be an active member of the Direct Selling Association. To view the DSA Code of Ethics, by which we abide, [click here](http://www.dsa.org/ethics/).

**Privacy Policy**

Zrii, LLC ("Zrii" or "our" or "we") realizes that your privacy is important and that your personal information must be protected. By visiting this website ("Site") or using any of the services offered on the Site, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. BEFORE YOU CAN PLACE AN ORDER, OR USE ANY OF OUR OTHER PRODUCTS AND SERVICES, YOU MUST AGREE TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF USE.

**1\. Information Collection**

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as filling your orders, responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our web services, and communicating with you. Typical information we store about you includes; name, main address, shipping address, tax ID, credit card number, email address, bank account number (if supplied), telephone and fax numbers.

Zrii collects information on the Site at two different stages. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information (such as domain name or IP address) from all visitors to the Site. When you are connected to the Internet, your computer has a unique Internet ID called an IP address. Most people that connect through a dial-up service, such as America Online, get a different IP address each time they login. Others logging in from work or school might have a permanently assigned IP address, called a static IP address. It is difficult or impossible for a website to collect personal information about you (i.e., your name, email address, etc.) from your IP address alone, although a static IP address can be used to identify a little bit more about you (i.e., your company name or university name).

Like many websites, we obtain certain types of information when your web browser contacts the Site. We store this information in small data repositories commonly called "cookies". The data stored in cookies enables our Site to recognize your browser and to provide features customized to you. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include: the temporary session ID, pages visited on the site, and which "pop-up" advertisements you have already seen. We store information that we collect through log files to create a profile of our users. Log files record IP addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. A profile is stored with information detailing how individual users use the Site. It is used solely for internal purposes, to help us improve the experience of our users. We do not share your profile with any third parties. The information we store in cookies does not include personal information, and Zrii only uses this information to make your visit to our Site better. However, some people prefer not to have cookies stored on their computers due to privacy concerns. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

Second, we require the submission of certain personally identifiable information when you use the services available on the Site. For example, your username and password allows us to identify you as a Zrii® Independent Executive.

To access most of the functionality at zrii.com, we require that you become a registered user and agree to comply with our Terms of Use. You must also choose a unique username and password, or use your ID and password to register as a zrii.com User and to access your account. To become a registered user, we require that you provide your name, and a valid and current email address, so that we may contact you, when necessary, concerning activity that is relevant to your account.

When you place an order, we require that you provide your name, mailing address, billing address, email address, phone number, credit card number and its expiration date. All of this information is necessary for us to complete the transaction and notify you of your order status. If you are ordering products for the first time, we also require that you choose a user name and password so that we can register you as a valid user. Finally, we maintain a history of the products you have ordered or saved to your account.

**2\. Personal Information of Children Under 13**

Zrii complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") and the Federal Trade Commission's rule interpreting COPPA (16 CFR § 512). This Site is not directed to children and we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age through this Site.

**3\. Use of Your Personal Information**

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, Zrii does not sell, rent, or share user information to or with any third party not affiliated with or owned by Zrii. Zrii will never give or sell your personal information to be used for the purposes of sending you unsolicited commercial offers (such as spam) from any third party. We will not ourselves use your personal information to send you unsolicited commercial offers. We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to provide quality customer support or to reach you regarding order status, product or fulfillment issues and other customer service related activities. We may use your email address, mailing address and/or phone number to contact you regarding new product offerings and other aspects of your use of the Site. If, however, you do not wish to receive such communications, you have the ability to "opt-out" at any time and you will not be contacted further.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and email, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These entities have access to personal information only when needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

**4\. Disclosure of Personal Information As Required By Law**

We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us; (2) protect and defend our rights; or (3) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others.

**5\. Business Transfers**

In the event Zrii goes through a business transition or a transfer, such as a merger, acquisition by another company or sale of a portion of its assets, or in the unlikely event that Zrii goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, our users' personal information may be part of the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Zrii or its assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we maintain full rights to any information collected on this Site, and may freely collect and use such information, unless prohibited by applicable law.

**6\. Links**

The Site contains links to other websites. Zrii is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**7\. Security**

Zrii takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your information. However, given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. We use technical and organizational security measures in order to protect the data we have under our control against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction, or against access by unauthorized persons. NEVERTHELESS, YOUR CONFIDENTIAL USE OF THIS SITE CANNOT BE GUARANTEED BY US. WE SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR HARM THAT YOU OR ANY PERSON MAY SUFFER AS A RESULT OF BREACH OF CONFIDENTIALITY IN RESPECT TO YOUR USE OF OUR SITE OR ANY INFORMATION YOU TRANSMIT TO OUR SITE.

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. SSL is a communication protocol that accomplishes two things: (1) It allows your web browser to verify that a web site you are visiting is actually the site that you think it is (and not some site posing as another); (2) It lets your web browser and a web server communicate with each other (i.e., pass web pages back and forth) in a completely secure fashion through the use of encryption techniques. This encrypted communication makes it impossible for anyone else to see any information passed between your web browser and our web server. You can tell that you are on a secure page when you see the lock on the bottom right of your browser.

When registering for access to a secure area of the Site, we will ask you to select a username and password. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Also, remember to sign out of the Site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence when accessing your computer.

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. We will also send you a confirmation of your order once it is complete.

We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

We also make an effort to protect your information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. All employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that store your personally identifiable information are housed in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about the security at our Site, you can send a message to the webmaster at: [webmaster@zrii.com](mailto:webmaster@zrii.com).

**8\. Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may contact us to correct, update or delete and deactivate our record of your personally identifiable information.

Retail customers and distributors can update or correct their personal information at any time by visiting the "My Zrii" section of the Site.

If you no longer wish to not receive any emails from Zrii you may opt-out by submitting your address to: [remove@zrii.com](mailto:remove@zrii.com).

**9\. Notification of Changes**

If the Privacy Policy changes materially so that your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you by e-mail to give you a choice as to whether or not we may use your information in this different manner. However, you are responsible for ensuring we have a current working e-mail address for you. If the e-mail address you have given us is incorrect or no longer operable, we will have no further obligation to notify you apart from posting the updated Privacy Policy on our Site.

**10\. Contact Information**

For further information about this site or Zrii products, please visit  
www.Zrii.com/pages/company/contact.xhtml

Effective: October 9, 2007
